DR. DINH DUC NHA NGUYEN (TONY)

Research Fellow



I have published 8 papers (six in Q1 journals) and one in a B-ranked conference, mentored students to publish high-impact publications, and contributed to an Elsevier book chapter. I have also received multiple awards for academic excellence, a successful grant application and international prize. With extensive industry experience and teaching roles at Deakin University, my expertise lies in cybersecurity, AI technology, network security and Quantum technology, particularly in machine learning and data science.

WORK EXPERIENCE

6.2023 – 11.2024 DEAKIN UNIVERSITY (AUSTRALIA)

2.2022 – 6.2023 DEAKIN UNIVERSITY (AUSTRALIA)

8.2017 – 2.2018 TECH JDI (VIETNAM)

3.2013 – 2.2017 TMA SOLUTIONS (VIETNAM)

ASSOCIATE RESEARCH FELLOW

• Industry project: implement automatically hybrid Quantum Cryptography (PQC) in digital signature in Virtual Private Network.

RESEACH ASSISTANT & TUTOR

- Conducted experiments and worked on publications for multiple projects in AI technology (machine learning models) and cybersecurity (IoT, IDS...).
- Taught three subjects in cybersecurity.

SENIOR TEST ENGINEER

• Delivered V-key platform, resulting in savings of 98K €.

TEST ANALYST & NETWORKING SPECIALIST

- Designed and executed test scenarios, test cases, and automated test scripts.
- Set up and configured the network topology for lab.

EDUCATION HISTORY

10.2020 – 6.2024 DEAKIN UNIVERSITY (AUSTRALIA)

Award Higher Degree Research. MASTER OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

semester 2 in 2019 and semester 1 in 2020.

7.2018 – 7.2020 QUEENSLAND UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY (AUSTRALIA)

(NETWORKS)Award: Awarded Dean's List for excellent academic performance in

DOCTOR OF PHILOSOPHY (CYBERSECURITY)

Award: School of Information Technology 2022 Student Excellence

INTERNATIONAL PRIZE

I have received Third Place in the 2022 Country to Country (C2C) Cybersecurity Challenge hosted by MIT, recognizing my skills in an international cybersecurity competition.

PUBLICATIONS

Visit my <u>Google Scholar Profile</u> and <u>IEEE Profile</u> for a complete list of publications. To date, I have published 8 journal papers (six Q1 paper) in IEEE venues and one IEEE conference (rank B).

CONTACT

Email: ndducnha@gmail.com Phone: (+61) 045 254 2713 Website: tonynguyen.work